
 const data = [
  {
   type: 'choice',
   question: 'It’s important that facilitators are aware of _____ that can occur online. ',
   answer: 'Assumptions and misinterpretations ',
   correct: 1,
   feedBackText: '',
  },
  {
   type: 'choice',
   question: 'As a facilitator, it is important to establish a ____ for conversations.',
   answer: 'Code of conduct ',
   feedBackText: '',
  },
  {
   type: 'choice',
   question: '_____ is a key facilitating skill that consists of keeping discussions moving.',
   answer: 'Weaving',
   feedBackText: '',
  },
  {
   type: 'choice',
   question: 'Facilitators should use their______ – this is how they represent themselves online and relate to others. ',
   answer: 'Social presence',
   correct: 1,
   feedBackText: '',
},
{
   type: 'choice',
   question: 'It is easy for misunderstandings to occur in online settings where the _____ cues are missing. ',
   answer: 'Physical and verbal ',
   feedBackText: '',
}];

export default data






// {
//    "questions": [
//       {
//          "type": 'choice',
//          "question": 'It’s important that facilitators are aware of _____ that can occur online. ',
//          "answer": 'Assumptions and misinterpretations ',
//          "correct": 1,
//          "feedBackText": '',
//       },
//       {
//          "type": 'choice',
//          "question": 'As a facilitator, it is important to establish a ____ for conversations.',
//          "answer": 'Code of conduct ',
//          "feedBackText": '',
//       },
//       {
//          "type": 'choice',
//          "question": '_____ is a key facilitating skill that consists of keeping discussions moving.',
//          "answer": 'Weaving',
//          "feedBackText": '',
//       },
//       {
//          "type": 'choice',
//          "question": 'Facilitators should use their______ – this is how they represent themselves online and relate to others. ',
//          "answer": 'Social presence',
//          "correct": 1,
//          "feedBackText": '',
//       },
//       {
//          "type": 'choice',
//          "question": 'It is easy for misunderstandings to occur in online settings where the _____ cues are missing. ',
//          "answer": 'Physical and verbal ',
//          "feedBackText": '',
//       }
//    ]
// }



// var buttonStartText = ['Start the clock!', 'Let’s do it!', 'I’m ready!', 'Bring it on!', 'Go!', 'Here we go!'];

// var defaultFeedbacks = {
//    correct: '<div class="popup-title"><img src="imgs/YesYouGotit-title.svg" class="img-responsive" alt="" /></div> <br>',
//    incorrect1: '<div class="popup-title"><img src="imgs/ThatisNotRight-title.svg" class="img-responsive" alt="" /></div> <br>',
//    incorrect2: '<div class="popup-title"><img src="imgs/ThatisNotRight-title.svg" class="img-responsive" alt="" /></div> <br>',
//    timeout: '<div class="popup-title" style="max-width:250px"><img src="imgs/TimeIsUp-Title.svg" class="img-responsive" alt="" /></div> Try to be quicker next time!'
// };
// var feedbackIcons = {
//    correct: '<span class="correct feedback-icon"><i class="fas fa-check"></i></span> ',
//    incorrect: '<span class="incorrect feedback-icon"><i class="fas fa-times"></i></div></span> ',
//    tip: '<span class=""><i class="fas fa-user-tie"></i></span> '
// };
// var actionMsgs = {
//    next: 'Ready for the next question?',
//    finish: 'OK, shall we find out where you rank on the leaderboard against the best players?'
// };


